A Guide to the Louis O. Kunkel papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA172
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence, 1930-1959; 3
  - Sm-St
    - Society of American Bacteriologists, 1937-1945; 25 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
      L.O. Kunkel, President (1942-1943) of Theobald Smith Society, NJ branch of; also member of program committee.
      Correspondence about workings as President and member of program committee.
      Includes Correspondence about Meetings: 1937 May 1 Princeton, N.J. (?) Eastern Pa chapter of the Society of American Bacteriologists. Paper delivered "Isolation of mild strains of aster yellows from heat-treated leafhoppers" with typescript of abstract. 1945 June 16 New Brunswick NJ Joint meeting of NJ and NYC branches of the Society of American Bacteriologists. Paper delivered "A new yellows disease of carrots". Also includes 1942 Oct pamphlet of the Theobald Smith Society with review of 1941-1942; officers and committees, directory of members.
    - Society of Arts and Sciences, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Socony Vacuum Corp, 1 item (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Soliman, A.A., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Sonoco Products Co., 4 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Sorencen, M., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Souphieff, L.O., 4 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - South Orange-Maplewood Adult School, 5 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Spelman, J.R., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Spring, D., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Spurr, A.R., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Stahel, G., 2 items (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Sthler, H., 1 item (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Spencer, Ernest L., 1932-1953; 58 items (Box 14, Folder 5)
      At RIMR 1932-1941
      Includes resume of Spencer's doctoral thesis and college transcript; recommendations for.
    - Stanley, Wendell M., 1931-1952; 48 items (Box 14, Folder 6)
      At RIMR 1931-1948.
      Includes recommendations for Stanley from W.J.V. Osterhaut and James B. Conant; typescript of Stanley biographical material for "America's Young Men" Vol III, 1938-39; curriculum vitae and 1932, 1940 bibliographies. Meetings: 1952 Oct 9-10 Berkeley, Univ. of California symposium on biochemistry and viruses held in conjunction with opening ceremonies for the new biochemistry and virus laboratory. Oct 10 paper delivered "Contributions of plant virus research".
      Includes program.
    - Steere, Russell L. At RIMR 1950-1951, 1950-1959; 39 items (Box 14, Folder 7)
      At RIMR 1950-1951.
      Includes college transcript and curriculum vitae. Kunkel holograph.
  - St-Sy (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Stakman, E.C., 1932-1953; 11 items
      Includes 1 item on Stakman retirement.
    - Starr, M.P., 2 items
    - Starrett, R.C., 2 items
    - Steele, J.M., 1937 January 29; 3 items
      Meeting: RIMR staff meeting. Paper delivered "High temperature reactions of yellow viruses"
    - Sterling Rubber Co. Ltd., 1 item
    - Stern, L.J., 1 item
    - Stevens, F.L., 2 items
    - Stevens, N.E. and R.B. (Father and son)., 1931-1954; 32 items
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues (N.E. Stevens)
    - Stewart, F.B., 9 items
    - Stewart, W.D., 1 item
    - Stillman, Edgar., 1932 November 17; 8 items
      Meeting: Harvey Society meeting at NY Academy of Medicine. Harvey Lecture by Kunkel "Similarities between diseases of the vegetable kingdom and those of man and animals"
    - Stoddard, E.M., 4 items
    - Stoll, Norman R., 2 items
    - Stoner, W.N., 4 items
    - Storey, H.H., 6 items
    - Stout, A.B., 10 items
    - Stout, G.L., 3 items
    - Strachan, A., 2 items
    - Strausbaugh, P.D., 2 items
    - Streed, A.M., 2 items
    - Strong, L.C. Seminar, 1935 December 5; 7 items
      Includes 1935 Dec 5 New Haven, Conn Yale Univ. seminar on atypical growth. Paper delivered on "immunity from plant virus diseases".
    - Suits, C.G., 2 items
    - Summers, E.M., 2 items
    - Sunderland, R.E., 2 items
    - Swan, H., 2 items
      On contribution toward painting of portrait of Florence Sabin on her 80 birthday; also birthday letter (copy not included)
    - Swift, H.F., 6 items
      Includes Correspondence about contributions in Celebration of A.E. Cohn's 60 birthday and R. Cole's 70 birthday [contributions not included].
    - Swift, M.E., 1934-1955; 7 items
      Includes recommendation for; and Kunkel holograph.
    - Swingle, C.F., 1 item
    - Sylvester, E.S., 2 items
    - Synthetic Nitrogen Products, 2 items
  - T-Th
    - Taft School, 1 item (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Tagliabue Mfg. Co. C.J., 1 item (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Takahashi, W.N., 6 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Takemori, N., 1 item (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Takeshita, R.M., 1 item (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Taliaferro, W.H., 4 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Tanaka, S., 1 item (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Tapley, W.T., 3 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Taylor, C.F., 3 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Taylor Instrument Companies, 2 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Taubenhaus, J.J., 6 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Taxy, S., 1 item (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Teachers Insurance & Annuity Assoc of America (TIAA), 2 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Tehon, L.R., 1931-1935 1945; 26 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Includes recommendation for C.N. Priode.
    - Temple, C.E., 4 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - ten Houten, J.G., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Tervet, I.W., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Teuscher, H., 6 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Thiel, A.F., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, Arthur H. Co., 4 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, Charles C., 4 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, H.E., 1931-1944; 11 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, H.R., 3 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, K.M., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Thomas, S., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Thompson, H.C., 4 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Thompson, L.S., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Thompson, R.C., 1941-1947; 15 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Thomson, R.B., 3 items (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Thornberry, H.H., 1931-1953; 109 items (Box 15, Folder 2)
      At RIMR 1931-1935. Includes 1946 Feb 8 Kunkel statement regarding participation of Staff members in war effort; some biographical material and recommendation for (For Correspondence Between J.A. McClintock and H.H. Thornberry see under: J.A. McClintock Box no. 10).
      No Subnote Content
  - Th-Ty (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Thung, T.H., 1 item
    - Thurston, G.L., 1 item
    - Thurlow, J.F., 12 items
      Includes some Correspondence with J.K. Scoggin.
    - Tiedjens, V.A., 2 items
    - Tippo, O., 1956; 6 items
      Includes recommendation for L.M. Black; 1 item on Kunkel receiving 1956 certificate of merit from Botanical Society of America at golden jubilee meeting.
    - Tirelli, M., 2 items
    - Tisdale, W.H., 2 items
    - Titusville Iron Works Co., 2 items
    - Tobacco By-Products and Chemical Corp, 1 item
    - Tobey, E.R., 2 items
      Recommendations for A.F. Ross and E.L. Spencer
    - Tompkins, C.M., 1934 1956; 14 items
    - Toothaker, L.A., 2 items
    - Torrey Botanical Club, 1936-1951; 20 items
      Includes Manuscript: 1950 Biographical sketch of Neil E. Stevens and Meeting: 1950 Dec 19 Columbia Univ., New York City Torrey Botanical Club meeting. Paper delivered "Yellows diseases of plants".
    - Tottingham, W.E., 2 items
      Recommendation for E.L. Spencer and A.F. Ross
    - Townsend, G.R., 3 items
    - Trelease, S.F. (Editor: American J Botany)., 1935-1949; 37 items
      Correspondence deals primarily with mss for publication in American J Botany by Kunkel and others; Kunkel Manuscripts: "Peach mosaic not cured by heat treatments"; "Effect of heat on ability of Cicadula sexnotata (Fall.) to transmit yellows"; includes recommendation for Dr. Price
    - Trumbower, J.A., 2 items
    - Tucek, M.A., 3 items
    - Tucker, C.M., 1935 1947; 4 items
    - Tukey, H.B., 1947 January 15; 17 items
      Deals primarily with Meeting: 1947 Jan 15 East Lansing, Mich. Michigan State College Fruit Growers Conference. Paper delivered "Virus diseases of plants"
    - Turner, W.F., 1 item
    - Tyler, W.S. Co., 2 items
  - U (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Ullstrup, A.J., 1935-1946; 27 items
      At RIMR 1935-1937. Includes some Ullstrup biographical material; and recommendation for.
    - Ungar, S.J., 2 items
    - UNESCO, 1 item
    - United States Dept of Agriculture (Office of Experiment Stations), 2 items
      Concerning Experiment Station Record
    - U.S. Dept of Agriculture (Office of Information), 1932 1942; 3 items
      Includes 1 item re: Plant Disease Reporter.
    - U.S. Dept of Agriculture (Yearbook)., 1953; 4 items
    - U.S. Govt Printing Office. Concerns purchase of government publications, 5 items
      Concerns purchase of government publications
    - U.S. State Department, 1 item
      Affirming Marjorie E. Swift loyalty to U.S.
    - University of Bombay, 4 items
      About examining N.C. Chatterjee thesis
    - University of California, Berkeley, 5 items
    - University of Missouri, 1933-1953; 19 items
      Deals with alumni activities. In 1934 ca. Dec. Dr. Kunkel elected permanent President of Class of 1909 and some Correspondence deals with workings as President.
      Includes Kunkel attends: 1933 Oct 26 Princeton, N.J. RIMR dinner honoring Dr. Robbins given by botanical group at Princeton; 1934 Nov 28-29. 25 anniversary reunion and 1949 ca. May 40 anniversary reunion of Class of 1909 University of Missouri.
    - University of North Carolina Press, 1 item
    - University of Wisconsin Library, 1 item
    - Uppal, B.N., 1933-1949; 29 items
      At RIMR from 1933 Dec for several months
    - Upton Nursery and Landscaping Co., 1 item
    - Utah Agricultural Experiment Station, 1 item
    - Utter, L.G., 2 items
  - V (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Vaida, A., 2 items
    - Valenta, V., 2 items
    - Valleau, W.D., 13 items
    - Vallega, J., 1 item
    - van der Planck, J.E., 1 item
    - van Der Water, C. Mrs, 5 items
    - van der Want, J.P.H., 4 items
    - Van Keuren, P.M., 2 items
    - Vanterpool, T.C., 6 items
    - Varma, P.M., 3 items
    - Varrelman, F.A., 5 items
    - Vaughan's Seed Store, 1 item
    - Verlag des Agrikulturchemischen Institutes, 2 items
    - Vermont Agricultural Experiment Station, 1 item
    - Verplancke, G., 1 item
    - Vestal, E.F., 2 items
    - Vinson, C.G., 1931-1937; 21 items
    - Virginia Agricultural Experiment Station, 2 items
    - Vocational Bureau of Skilled Workers, 1 item
      Recommendation for H. Plantenga
    - Vollert, H.E., 5 items
    - Voorhees, R.K., 1 item
    - Vuittenez, A., 2 items
  - W-We (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Wade, B.L., 1 item
    - Waite, M.B., 7 items
    - Waksman, S.A., 1933 February 6; 4 items
      Seminar: 1933 Feb. 6 New Brunswick, N.J. Agricultural Experiment Station, Dept of Soil Microbiology seminar. Paper delivered "The historical development of our knowledge of plant viruses"
    - Waldee, E.L., 14 items
    - Walker-Gordon Laboratory Co., 2 items
    - Walker, E.A., 1 item
    - Walker, J.C., 1932 1950; 8 items
    - Wall, M.E., 4 items
    - Wallace, H.A., 2 items
    - Wallin, J.R., 4 items
    - Walter, J.M., 6 items
    - Walters, H.J., 2 items
    - Ward, R.B., 1 item
    - Warmke, H.E., 1941 1947; 2 items
    - Warren, A.J., 1 item
    - Washburne, J.S., 2 items
      Recommendation for Mrs. R.B. Healey
    - Watkins, T.C., 2 items
    - Watson, A.J., 2 items
    - Watson, M., 2 items
    - Waverly Press, 4 items
    - Weather Bureau, 1 item
    - Weathers, L.G., 1 item
    - Weber, W.M., 1 item
    - Webster, L.T., 6 items
      Includes comments on Webster talk.
    - Weddle, C., 1943-1954; 12 items
    - Wegrich, O.G., 6 items
    - Weidman, W.M., 2 items
    - Weier, T.E., 8 items
    - Weigel, C.A., 3 items
    - Weimer, B.R., 3 items
  - We-Wes
    - Weindling, R., 5 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Weinmann, R., 5 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Weinstein, F., 1936; 3 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Includes Kunkel biographical data with bibliography and listing of Kunkel outstanding achievements to 1936 Feb.
    - Weinstein, L.H., 7 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Weiss, F., 1932-1942; 14 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Includes: Meetings: 1935 ca. Apr 23 Washington, D.C. NAS meeting; 1935 Apr. 24 Washington, D.C. Botanical Society of Washington symposium on virus diseases of animals and plants. Paper delivered "Summary of plant virus diseases".
    - Weiss, Paul A., 3 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Includes Weiss and Collaborators bibliography.
    - Weissman, G.S., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Welch, D.S., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Welch, W.M. Mfg. Co., 1 item (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Wellington, R., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Wellman, F.L., 4 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Wellhausen, E.J., 1936-1949; 47 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Wernham, C.C., 4 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Westcott, C., 3 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Westdal, P.H., 2 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Weston, W.H., 3 items (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - White, Philip R., 1931-1954; 106 items (Box 15, Folder 8)
      At RIMR 1932-1945. Includes fellowships and other recommendations for; and White holographs.
  - Wh-Wi (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Whetzel, H.H., 1932-1944; 18 items
    - White, J.S., 1 item
    - White, O.E., 1935-1952; 14 items
      Professional Correspondence between colleagues socially friendly. Includes recommendation for W.C. Price and White holographs. [See also under: Blandy Experimental Farm Box no. 5].
    - White, R.P., 3 items
    - Whitehouse, W.E., 2 items
    - Whipple, O.C., 1 item
    - Wiggans, R.G., 14 items
    - Wilbrink, G., 2 items
    - Wilcox, R.B., 1942-1949; 7 items
    - Wilde, W.H.A., 2 items
    - Wildman, S.G., 1952 October 13; 9 items
      Includes: Seminar: 1952 Oct 13 Los Angeles, Calif. Univ. of Calif. Div of Botany seminar [Title?] and recommendation for research grant for.
    - Wilhelm, S., 2 items
    - Will Corp., 7 items
    - Williams, E.J., 2 items
    - Williams, H.E., 1 item
    - Williams, W.L., 4 items
  - Wi-Wy (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Williams & Wilkins Co., 6 items
      Concerns Kunkel publications.
    - Wilson, E.B., 1 item
    - Wilson, I.D., 2 items
      Recommendation for E.M. Hildebrand
    - Wilson, R.A., 2 items
    - Wilson, R.D., 1 item
    - Windsor Co., 17 items
      On purchasing supplies, cloth, needles etc
    - Wingard, S.A., 1934-1942; 3 items
    - Winter, F.L., 1 item
    - Winters, R.Y., 2 items
    - Wisconsin Agricultural Experiment Station, 1 item
    - Witherow, J.L., 2 items
    - Woglom, W.H., 4 items
    - Wolf, D.E., 1 item
    - Wolf, F.A., 1932-1949; 10 items
    - Wood, T.W. & Sons, 4 items
    - Woodbury, C.G., 3 items
    - Woodhams, G.E., 2 items
    - Woods, A.F., 4 items
    - Woods, M.W., 1931-1936 1946; 25 items
      Includes photographs of slides showing the structures resembling intracellular bodies with memorandums concerning slides.
      Includes Kunkel's comments and suggestions on slides, investigative work and mss.
    - Woodward, C.H. Manuscript, 1937; 6 items
      Includes typescript of Kunkel review of "A textbook of plant virus diseases" by Kenneth M. Smith, P. Blakiston's Son & Co., Inc. Philadelphia 1937 [Editor's note: This review is not included with Kunkel bibliography].
    - World Biography, 1953; 1 item
    - World Calendar Association, 3 items
    - Worthley, H.N., 2 items
    - Wortmann, D., 2 items
    - Wright, C.M., 2 items
    - Wright, N.S., 9 items
    - Writer's Board, 1 item
    - Wyckoff, R.W.G., 5 items
      See also under: Smith, K.M. letter of recommendation for Smith in Box no. 14
    - Wyers, D., 1 item
    - Wyeth, G.A., 2 items
    - Wylie, R.B., 2 items
    - Wyoming Agricultural Experiment Station, 1 item
  - Y (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Yale University Press, 1 item
    - Yarwood, C., 1937-1956; 5 items
    - Yenching University, 2 items
    - Young, H.C., 2 items
    - Young, P.A., 1934-1946; 11 items
    - Young, R.R., 2 items
    - Younkin, S.G., 1943-1951; 14 items
  - Zimmerman, P.W., 1933-1953; 27 items (Box 16, Folder 4)
    Professional Correspondence between colleagues socially friendly. Includes: Meeting: 1942 June 24 Yonkers, NY Boyce Thompson Institute, Torrey Botanical Club anniversary meeting. Paper delivered "on viruses in relation to growth in plants".
  - Z (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Zaleski, K., 2 items
    - Zaumeyer, W.J., 1 item
    - Zeliff, C.C., 3 items
    - Zeller, S.M., 1 item
    - Zelley, J.W., 2 items
    - Zentmyer, G., 1 item
    - Zichis, J., 2 items
    - Zilles, J.A., 1 item
    - Zundel, G.L., 1932 1944-1945; 8 items
- Laboratory notes, 1928-1956; 4 (Box 17)
  Photographic prints of various virus diseased plants with experimental data (loose leaf covers removed - some years lacking); includes literature searches of virus disease literature to and including 1929.
  - Virus disease literature to and including 1929, 3 folders
    Includes: subject index pp i-ii; author index pp iii-ixxviii; literature citations pp 1-276. Stapled items found in duplicate copy (inserted where found); other items found in original copy and kept in order found (papers and references).
    - pp 1-85 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - pp 86-178 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - pp 179-276 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Photographic Prints, 1928-1956
    Notebooks containing photographic prints with experimental work descriptions of virus diseases in plants; some tables.
    Includes table of contents; index to prints listing page number; lantern slide number (lantern slides 1928-1945 only) and negative number (negatives 1933-1956 only); some negatives found. (Description from original loose leaf covers). There are lapses in dates of notebooks (some years lacking).
    - Aster yellows etc., 1928-1937; 2 folders
      - Includes 3 pages of table of contents; 2 pages lantern slide and negative index; pp 1-69 of photographs with experiments (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - pp 70-124 photographs with experiments (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Peach yellows, rosette, potato malnutrition, tomato spotted wilt etc., 1928-1934; 2 folders
      - Includes 2 pages of table of contents; 2 pages lantern slide and negative index; pp 1-69 of photographs with experiments (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - pp 70-124 photographs with experiments (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Peach: Yellows, rosette, 1933-1936 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Includes 1 page table of contents; 1 page negative and lantern slide index; pp 1-38 photographs with experiments.
    - Photographs of various diseased plants: Alfalfa, aster etc..., 1942-1945; 2 folders
      (Table of contents alphabetically lists plants and diseases) Sept. 1942-April 1945 [Editor's note: Page numbers referred to are those typed in black ink, not handwritten red ink ones]
      - Includes title page; 1 page negative and lantern slide index; 7 pages table of contents; pp 1-50 photographs with experiments (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - pp 51-105 photographs with experiments (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Photographs of various diseased plants: Alfalfa witches' broom, apple, aster etc..., 1945-1947; 2 folders
      (table of contents alphabetically lists plants and diseases May 1945-Nov 1947 [Editor's note: Page numbers referred to are those typed in black ink, not handwritten red ink ones]
      - Includes title page; 1 page negative and lantern slide index; 5 pages table of contents; pp 1-49 photographs with experiments (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - pp 50-108 photographs with experiments (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Photographs of various diseased plants: Abutilon, alfalfa, asclepias etc..., 1948-1949; 2 folders
      (table of contents alphabetically lists plants and diseases) Jan. 1948- Nov. 1949 [Editor's note: page numbers referred to are those typed in black ink, not handwritten red ink ones]
      - Includes: Title page; 1 page negative and lantern slide index; 7 pages of table of contents; pp 1-59 photographs with experiments (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - pp 60-120 photographs with experiments (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Photographs of various diseased plants: Aster, aster yellows, California aster yellows etc., 1954-1956 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      (table of contents alphabetically lists plants and diseases) 1954 Oct-1956 Sept [Editor's note: Page numbers referred to are those typed in black, ink;, not handwritten red ink ones].
      Includes: Title page; 1 page photograph number index; 8 pages table of contents; pp 1-45 photographs with experiments.
- Lantern Slides, 5
  - Lantern slide card file index, numbers 1-537, 1928-1945
    Includes RI lantern slide number; negative number; plant virus information (negatives begin with 1933 to 1956 and some found).
    - Experimental work of various diseased plants, 1928-1945; 3 4 lantern slides (Box 20)
      Slide description on each slide and box description on outside and inside of some boxes. (Negatives begin with 1933 and some negatives of slides found). In 11 wooden boxes.
  - Glass Slides, 6
    - Aster and peach yellows, RI 1-47 (Box 21-1)
    - Peach yellows and rosette, RI 48-82 (Box 22-2)
    - Abutilon, corn, potato, (RI 135 rose, saint-paulia, tob. lacking) ring spot, etc..., RI 83-135 (Box 23-3)
    - Tobacco ringspot, sandal, sida, sugar cane, galls, Aucuba mosaic, etc..., RI 136-184 - (Box 24-4)
    - Hippeastrum, corn, pea, curly top, seeds, Boyce Thompson, Aucuba and tob. mosaics, etc..., RI 185-234 (Box 25-5)
    - Aucuba and tob. mosaics, wheat mosaic, etc..., RI 235-292 (Box 26-6)
    - Miscellaneous 1937-1943 lacking 337-339, RI 293-342 (Box 27-7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1938-1943; RI 343-388 (Box 28-8)
    - None, RI 389-438 (Box 29-9)
    - None, RI 439-488 (Box 30-10)
    - None, RI 489-537 (Box 31-11)
- Photographic negatives, 1933-1956; 6; 1014 envelopes of 5 7 photographic negatives in 3 boxes
  Experimental work of various diseased plants; some tables.
  Includes some 5x7 glass negatives and prints in Box nos. 32 and 33. Some envelopes contain more than 1 negative. Lantern slides of some negatives found.
  Arranged in chronological order.
  - 1933-1937 (Box 32)
    - 1933, 56 envelopes
      Includes 2 prints.
    - 1934, 68 items
      Includes 5 prints.
    - 1935, 52 items
      Includes 1 print.
    - 1936, 75 items
      Includes 6 prints.
    - 1937, 58 items
  - 1938-1945 (Box 33)
    - 1938, 12 items
      Includes 3 prints; (1 duplicate).
    - 1939, 62 items
      Includes 5 envelopes of 3x4 negatives.
    - 1940, 48 items
    - 1941, 46 items
    - 1942, 49 items
      Includes 2 prints; (1 duplicate).
    - 1943, 53 items
    - 1944, 32 items
    - 1945, 82 items
  - 1946-1956 (Box 34)
    - 1946, 28 items
    - 1947, 33 items
    - 1948, 54 items
    - 1949, 49 items
    - 1950, 30 items
    - 1951, 19 items
    - 1952, 11 items
    - 1953, 14 items
    - 1954, 54 items
    - 1955, 24 items
    - 1956, 5 items
- Collected Reprints, 1912-1961; 3 volumes
  - Volume 1, 1912-1924
  - Volume 2, 1925-1938
  - Volume 3, 1939-1961